I. Feinberg, Robert Arbitration Records 5548
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Ronson Corp. of Penn. And IAM, Dist. 128, Local Lodge #1724. 5/11/66, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1724)
  Decision: Super seniority; Union representative and business; Demotions. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. This case examines the status of super seniority of union representatives after their term of office.
- American Sugar Co. and ILA, Local 9. 9/21/66, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1725)
  Decision: Assignment of jobs; Seniority. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Co. and Peninsula Shipbuilders' Assn. 9/13/66, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1726)
  Decision: Discharge; Improper job attitude; Improper work practices. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan New York, Inc. and N.Y. Typographical Union #6, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1727)
  [File A] (for Haber Typographers) 9/9/66. Decision: Contract interpretation; Absences; Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. [File B] (for Peter F. Mallon) 9/9/66. Decision: Compensation; Inability to work; M
- The Whitney Chain Division Hewitt-Robins Inc. and UAW, Local Union #119. 9/28/66, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1728)
  Decision: Insurance. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Detroit Steel Corp. and USA. 11/17/66, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1730)
  Decision: Transfers; Shift scheduling. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Armstrong Cork Co., Lancaster Floor Plant and URW, Local #285. 12/29/66, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1731)
  Decision: Assignment to work outside classification. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Public Service Electric and Gas Co. and Office Employees Int'l Union, Local 153. 2/2/67, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 1732)
  Decision: Assignment of new jobs; Classification of jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Sprague & Henwood, Inc. and IAM, Dist. 128, Lodge #1971 AFL-CIO 1/3/67, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 1733)
  Decision: Insurance. Contains notes and correspondence.
- American Building Maintenance Co. and TWU, Local 504 2/9/67, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 1734)
  Decision: Termination of business; Successor company; Severance pay. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- General Aniline and Film Corp. and IAM, Johnson City Lodge #1807 3/3/67, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 1735)
  Decision: Transfers; Shift scheduling; Managements rights. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. and OCAW, Local 8-2340 AFL-CIO 2/15/67, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 1736)
  Decision: Discharge; Alcoholism, drinking and intoxication. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits
- Oline Mathieson Chemical Corp. and IAM, Lodge #609, AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 1737)
  [File A] 4/3/67. Decision: Vacations and vacation pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. [File B] 5/8/67. Decision: Discharge; Improper work practices; Plant rules; Safety. Contains notes, correspondence, and agreements.
- N.Y. Engineering Co. and IBT, Local 810. 2/10/67, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 1738)
- Shenango, Inc. and USA, AFL-CIO. 4/13/67 [Files A&B], 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1739)
  Decision: Quits; Absences. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Mainway Warehouse, Inc. and IBT, General Warehousemen's Local 892 4/19/67 (Box 20, Folder 1740)
  Decision: Promotion; Training and trial periods; Employees rights. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Univac Division of Sperry Rand Corp. and IUE, Local 165, AFL-CIO. 4/26/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1741)
  Decision: Arbitrability; Absences; Tardiness; Plant rules. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Peter J. Schweitzer, Inc., Division of Kimberly Clark Corp. and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 482, AFL-CIO 4/18/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1742)
  Decision: Contract modification; Classification of jobs; Rates of pay; Evaluation of job factors. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Elizabeth Works, Industrial Chemicals Div., Allied Chemical Corp. and OCAW, Local #8-166, AFL-CIO. 8/9/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1743)
  Decision: Contract silence; Lunch periods. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Clark Equipment Co. and IAM, Dist. 47, Lodge 1697, AFL-CIO. 6/5/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1744)
  Decision: Duty to bargain; Past practice. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits. An interesting view of the scope of the arbitrator's authority vis--vis past practice is afforded.
- Int'l Nickel Co., Inc. and USA, Local #40, AFL-CIO 6/22/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1745)
  Decision: Overtime; Premium pay; Management rights. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- R.C. Can Co. and IAM, Dist. 65, Local #1644, AFL-CIO. 6/27/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1746)
  Decision: rates of pay; Classification of jobs; Management rights. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Whitney Blake Co. and UE, Local 299 5/25/67., 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1747)
  Decision: Discharge; Improper work practices; Equipment and physical facilities. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- United Press Int'l, Inc. and Commercial Telegraphers Union, United Press System Div. #47, AFL-CIO 8/29/67 [Files A&B], 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1748)
  Decision: Removal of work from bargaining unit; Jurisdiction. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Allied Silversmiths Assn., Inc. and Amalgamated Silver and Allied Metal Workers Union, (JWU), Local 38. 6/7/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1749)
  Decision: Premium pay; Holidays and holiday pay; Work week. Contains notes, correspondence and agreements.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y. (for Gould Typographers, Inc.) and N.Y. Typographers Union #6 8/15/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1751)
  Decisions: 1) Arbitrability. 2) Applications for employment; Jurisdiction; Supervisors and foremen; Testing of employees. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- General Dynamics Corp. and CJA, Local 1302. 9/18/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1753)
  Decision: Assignment to work outside classification; Past practice. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Free Europe Inc. and Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3. 6/27/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1754)
  Decision: Retirement; Contract interpretation. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Shieldalloy Corp. and RWDSU, Dist. 65, AFL-CIO. 8/15/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1756)
  Decision: removal of work from the bargaining unit; Supervisors and foremen. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Sylvestro Polchetti, doing business as Bronx County Carting Co. and IBT, Private Sanitation Local 813. 11/22/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1757)
  Decision: Contractual duties; refusal to pay; crew size; welfare funds; union security; insurance; pension plans. Contains notes, correspondence and agreements.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (for Thomas A. Koppel & Son Co., Inc.) and N.Y. Typographical Union #6. 9/5/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1758)
  Decision: Layoff; notice; employees rights. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Shenango Inc. and USA, Local 2258, AFL-CIO. 10/19/67 (Box 20, Folder 1760)
  Decision: Rates of pay; Overtime; Past Practice. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Scovill Mfg. Co. and UAW, Local 1604, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 1762)
  [File A] 1/17/68. Decision: Contracting out. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. [File B] 4/7/69. Decision: Contracting out; Past practice. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- J.R. Stevenson Corp. and Metallic Lathers' Union of N.Y. and Vicinity, Local 46. 1/4/68, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 1764)
  Decision: Layoffs; Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages; damages. Contains notes and correspondence
- Thomasset Colors Division of Starling Drug, Inc. and OCAW, Local 8-406. 12/28/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1765)
  Decision: Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Phelps Dodge Refining Corp. Laurel Hill Plant and USA, Local Union #4355, AFL-CIO, 10/1/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1766)
- American Car and Foundry Division, ACF Industries, Inc. and USA Local 1652. 4/10/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1768)
  Decision: Discharge; insubordination; fights and altercations. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Capitol Records, Inc. and IAM, Dist. 128, Record Lodge #1963 2/15/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1770)
  Decision: Unemployment benefits; Quits. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- E.I. DuPont DeNemours & Co. and United Chemical Workers. 9/6/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1771)
  Decision: Demotion; incompetence and inefficiency. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- General Cable Corp. and IAM, Dist. 157, Local Lodge 2101 3/18/68 [Files A&B], 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1772)
  Decisions: 1) Withdrawal of existing benefits; Lunch periods; classification of jobs. 2) Call-in. 3) Overtime; transfers; departments. 4) Seniority; bidding; testing of employees; ability. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- American Buslines Inc. and ATU, Div. #1133, AFL-CIO. 4/5/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1773)
  Decision: Discharge; insubordination. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Brewer Dry Dock Co. and Brewer Dry Dock Employees Assn., Inc. 3/21/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1774)
  Decision: Call-in; notice. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Rochester Telephone Corp. and CWA, AFL-CIO. 5/6/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1775)
  Decision: Retroactive pay; Assignment to new jobs; Overtime; Past practice. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Charles G. Summers, Jr., Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters & Butchers Workmen of N. America, Local 295, AFL-CIO. 4/11/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1776)
  Decision: Vacation pay; Retirement. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. In this case, "vacation pay has been recognized, in recent years, to constitute a form of wages which have been earned by the employee during the period preceding
- E.I. DuPont DeNemours and Co. and Parlin Employees' Assn., Inc. 6/25/68 [Files A&B], 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1777)
  Decision: Assignment to work outside classification; Duty to bargain; Classification of jobs; Rates of pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Stella D'Oro Biscuit Co., Inc. and Bakery Drivers Union Local 550. 4/8/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1778)
  Decisions: Vacation pay, Holidays and holiday pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Coast Metals, Inc. and UAW, Local 669, AFL-CIO. 4/22/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1780)
  Decision: Reinstatement; Discharge; Insubordination. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Ford Instrument Co. and IUE, Local 471, AFL-CIO. 7/9/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1781)
- The F & M Schaefer Brewing Co. and IAM, Lodge 186, AFL-CIO. 7/10/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1782)
  Decision: Vacation pay; shift scheduling; past practice. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. This case revolves around the pay rate upon which vacation pay is based; specifically if the employee is scheduled to work overtime on the we
- Houdaille Industries, Inc. and USA, Local 3739, AFL-CIO. 7/16/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1783)
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (for United States Banknote Corp.) and N.Y. Typographical Union #6 5/28/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1784)
  Decision: Discharge; Improper personal conduct; Improper job attitude; Plant rules. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Wayne Pump Co., Div. of Symington Wayne Corp. and IAM, Lodge 2138, AFL-CIO. 7/18/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1787)
- New York Times Co. and Newspaper Guild of N.Y. 7/22/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1788)
  Decision: Promotions. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. This case examines the complex situation which occurs when promotions are cancelled after a few days.
- Standard Brands Inc., Fleishmann Mfg. Div. and Int'l Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal Soft Drink and Distillery workers of America, Local 42, AFL-CIO. 10/17/68, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1789)
  Decisions: Call-in pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- Pratt & Whitney, Inc. and UAW, Unity Lodge, Amalgamated Local 405, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1792)
  [File A] 4/16/69. Decision: Suspension; strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits. [File B] 6/10/69. Decision: Bidding; promotions (down in pay); seniority. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibit
- Reliable Steel Drum Co., Inc. and UE, Local 292 11/4/68, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1793)
  Decisions: 1) Rates of pay; classification of jobs; evaluation of job factors. 2) Rates of pay; premium pay. 3) Premium pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. and N.Y. Typographical Union #6. 11/8/68, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1795)
  Decision: Vacation and vacation pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Powell-Savory Corp. d/b/a the Amsterdam News and Newspaper Guild of N.Y. 6/20/69, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1796)
  Decision: Compensation (commissions). Contains notes and correspondence.
- Pratt & Whitney, Inc. and UAW, Unity Lodge, Local 405, AFL-CIO. 1/20/69, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1798)
- Radio Corp. of America and IUE, Local 103, 106 and 110, AFL-CIO. 11/5/69 [Files A-C], 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1799)
  Decisions: Compensation; Refusal to pay; overtime; union representatives and business; grievances and grievance procedure. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (for Publishers Printing-Admiral Press, Inc.) and N.Y. Typographical Union #6. 3/17/69, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1800)
  Decision: discharge; fights and altercations; negligence and carelessness. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- N.Y. Telephone Co. and CWA, AFL-CIO. 7/10/69, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1801)
- Wyckoff Steel Div. of the Screw and Bolt Corp. of America and IAM, Dist. 47, Lodge 340 7/14/69, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1803)
  Decision: suspension; plant rules. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Mobil Oil Corp. and Independent Oil Workers 7/17/70, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 1804)
  Decision: premium pay; overtime; schedules of work. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Int'l Smelting and Refining Co. and USA, Local 4985, AFL-CIO. 8/18/69, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1805)
  Decision: discharge; insubordination; improper personal conduct. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Detroit Steel Corp. Easter Plant and USA, AFL-CIO. 8/25/69, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1806)
  Decisions: Insurance; Definitions. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. In this case, there is an application for insurance benefits for the Grievants dependent grandson. This issue is, of course, does the grandchild fall into the "dep
- United Aircraft Corp., Pratt & Whitney Aircraft Div., Southington Plant and IAM, Lodge 1746A, AFL-CIO. 1/14/70, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 1807)
  Decision: Holiday and holiday pay; Absences; Funeral leave and funeral pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits. This case involves a dispute over holiday pay centering around the contractual obligation of an employee to work the day
- Western Electric Co., Inc. (Kearny Works) and IBEW, Local #1470 [Files A&B] (Box 22, Folder 1808)
  Decision: contract interpretation; definitions. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Rochester Telephone Corp. and CWA, AFL-CIO. 8/24/71, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 1809)
  Decision: Assignment to work outside classification; Classification of jobs; Past practice. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- City of N.Y., Dept. of Marine and Aviation and Marine Engineers Beneficial Assn., Dist. #1 11/21/69, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 1810)
  Decision: Removal of work from the bargaining unit; temporary employees. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Pratt & Whitney, Inc. and UAW, Unity Lodge, Amalgamated Local 405 AFL-CIO. 2/5/70, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1811)
  Decision: layoffs; bumping; ability. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- United States Metals Refining Co. and USA, AFL-CIO 12/11/69, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 1812)
  Decision: Arbitrability; contract interpretation. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- United Aircraft Corp., Pratt & Whitney Aircraft Div. and IAM, Local 700 2/27/70 [Files A&B], 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1813)
  Decision: discharge; insubordination. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- N.Y. Telephone Co. and CWA, AFL-CIO 6/15/70, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1814)
  Decision: Suspension; strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages; union representatives and business. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. In this case, the role of the union representative during a strike, slowdown or work stoppage is disc
- United Aircraft Corp., Pratt & Whitney Aircraft Division, Florida Research & Development Center and IAM, Lodge 971. 7/9/70, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1816)
- Flushing Cemetery Assn. and Cemetery Workers and Green Attendants Union. 7/14/70, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1818)
  Decision: Pension plans. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- J. Weinig & Son and Weinig Fur Trading Corp. and FLM Joint Board, AFL-CIO. 6/10/70, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1819)
  Decision: reduction in force. Contains notes, correspondence and agreements.
- Gries Reproducer Co. and the Watch & Jewelry Workers Union, Local 147 AFL-CIO 7/24/70, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1820)
  Decision: Assignment to work outside classification; Managements rights. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- N.Y. City Transit Authority and Subway Supervisors Assn. 12/22/70 [Files A-C], 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1821)
  Decision: Withdrawal of existing benefits (meal allowances). Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Elizabeth Daily Journal and N.J. Newspaper Guild 11/10/70, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1823)
  Decision: Jurisdiction. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- The Foregger Co., Inc. and IUE, Local 463, AFL-CIO 12/4/70, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1824)
  Decision: Rates of pay; cost of living increases. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- United Aircraft Corp., Hamilton Standard Div. and IAM, Lodge 743 2/25/71, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1825)
  Decision: Holiday pay; Absences; Funeral leave. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. (see also: case 1808)
- United Aircraft Corp., Pratt & Whitney Aircraft Div., East Hartfield Plant and IAM Lodge 1746, AFL-CIO 2/25/71 [Files A-C], 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1826)
  Decision: Holiday and holiday pay; absences; funeral leave. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Music Fair Enterprises and AAA-AEA 10/23/70, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1827)
  Decision: overtime. Contains notes, correspondence, and agreements.
- The Connecticut Co. and ATU, Div. 425, AFL-CIO 2/16/71, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1828)
  Decision: discharge; alcoholism, drinking and intoxication. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. "An employer may discharge an employee who has been arrested for committing a criminal offense during working hours when it has no more ev
- United Aircraft Corp., Pratt & Whitney Aircraft Division and IAM, Lodge #700. 8/16/71 [Files A&B], 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1829)
  Decision: Discharge; improper personal conduct; plant rules. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y. (for Peter F. Mallon, Inc.) (Box 24, Folder 1830)
  Decision: Discharge; improper personal conduct. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- The Western Union Telegraph Co. and UTW, AFL-CIO. 4/15/71 [Files A&B], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1831)
  Decision: assignment to work outside classification; apprentices. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Board of Higher Education of the City of New York and Legislative Conference. 6/7/71 [Files A-C], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1832)
  Decision: Grievances and grievances procedure. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- League of Off-Broadway Theatres and Producers and AAA-AEA 5/25/71, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1833)
  Decision: Contract negotiations. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. This case is important as it covers the full scale negotiation of a contract. In this regard, the case should be noted, as it sets, for the first time, minimum wage
- ITT World Communications, Inc. and CWA, AFL-CIO 6/22/71 [Files A&B], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1834)
  Decision: arbitrability, timeliness. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Board of Higher Education of the City of New York (CUNY) and the Legislative Conference of the City University of N.Y. (for Georgia Rave) 6/28/71 [Files A&B], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1835)
  Decision: discriminatory treatment; training and trial periods. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits. This is an interesting case involving the tenure system. Also important is the stumbling block of the "Nota Bene"
- Midtown Chevrolet-Pontiac and IBT, Local #868 4/30/71, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1836)
  Decisions: 1) Discharge; standards of production (Sales). 2) Employee rights; equipment and physical facilities; Contract silence. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- New Jersey Bell Telephone Co. and Telephone Workers Union of New Jersey, Local 827, IBEW, AFL-CIO 9/27/71 [Files A&B], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1838)
  Decision: overtime; premium pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. The issue here involves the "doubling" of overtime and premium pay; that is, when the premium pay accrues to the same hours worked for different reasons (work at tim
- Mobil Oil Corp. and Radio Officers' Union of the United Telegraph Workers 6/28/71, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1839)
- Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y. (for Bowne & Co. of N.Y., Inc.) and Printing Utilities Branch of Typographical Union #6 (ITU) AFL-CIO, 5/10/71, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1840)
  Decision: Discharge; absenteeism. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- David Merrick ("Four on a Garden") and AAA-AEA (for Barry nelson) 9/9/71 [Files A&B], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1841)
  Decision: Discharge; insubordination; ability. Contains correspondence and exhibits.
- Bd. Of Ed. Of N.Y.C. and UFT, Local 2, AFT, AFL-CIO 11/9/72 [Files A&B] (Box 24, Folder 1842)
  Decision: Back pay award; assignment of new jobs; seniority. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits. This case is very important as it represents the first time that an arbitrator recommended a back-pay remedy in dealing with grievance su
- Printers League Section and N.Y. Typographical Union #6 6/29/71, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1843)
  Decision: Holidays and holiday pay; temporary employees; part time employees. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Standard Brands, Inc. and Int'l Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local Union 42 10/21/71, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1846)
  Decisions: 1) Holiday and holiday pay; call-in. 2) Call-in pay; overtime. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.